{
  "translations": {
    "en": {
      "fa1": "../../../AV/VisFormalLang/NFA/AutomataFiles/NFA2DFA2a.jff",
      "q1": {
        "type": "select",
        "src": "../../../AV/Development/formal_language/FAEditor.html",
        "question": "Which of the following are  alphabet sets?",
        "answer": ["{$a$, $b$, $c$}", "{0, 1}", "{?, $a$, $x$}"],
        "choices": ["{$a$, $b$, $c$}", "{0, 1}", "$A$", "{?, $a$, $x$}"]
      },
      "q2": {
        "type": "select",
        "src": "../../../AV/Development/formal_language/FAEditor.html",
        "question": "Suppose we have $\\Sigma$ = {$a$, $b$}, which of the following are valid strings?",
        "answer": ["$babababbaba$", "$a$"],
        "choices": ["$babababbaba$", "$a$", "{$aaa$, $bbb$}", "$bacbabcba$"]
      },
      "q2_2": {
        "type": "textBox",
        "question": "Why not answer c) {$aaa$, $bbb$} ?",
        "answer": "it is a set"
      },
      "q2_3": {
        "type": "textBox",
        "question": "Why not answer d) $bacbabcba$ ?",
        "answer": "it uses symbols not in question"
      },
      "q3": {
        "type": "select",
        "question": "What states can be combined?",
        "answer": [
          "$\\Sigma$={$0,1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8, 9\\}$ $L=\\{0,1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10,11,12,13,14,15,16,17,...\\}$",
          "$\\Sigma$={$a,b,c\\}$ $L=\\{ab,ac,cabb\\}$",
          "$\\Sigma$={$0,1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8, 9\\}$ $L=\\{set of all even numbers\\}$"
        ],
        "choices": [
          "$\\Sigma$={$0,1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8, 9\\}$ $L=\\{0,1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10,11,12,13,14,15,16,17,...\\}$",
          "$\\Sigma$={$a,b,c\\}$ $L=\\{ab,ac,cabb\\}$",
          "$\\Sigma$={$0,1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8, 9\\}$ $L=\\{set of all even numbers\\}$"
        ]
      },
      "q3_2": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "Is this one a langue?  $\\Sigma$=${a,b,c}$ $L = ab$",
        "answer": "No",
        "choices": ["Yes", "No"]
      },
      "q3_3": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "Is this one a langue?  $\\Sigma$=${a,b,c}$ $L = {a}$",
        "answer": "Yes",
        "choices": ["Yes", "No"]
      },
      "q3_4": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "Is this one a langue?  $\\Sigma$=${a,b,c}$ $L$ = {}",
        "answer": "Yes",
        "choices": ["Yes", "No"]
      },
      "q3_5": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "Oh, and remember that we have a special symbol for “empty” set. Which is it?",
        "answer": "{}",
        "choices": ["$\\Sigma$", "$E$", "{}"]
      },
      "q4": {
        "type": "textBox",
        "question": "List the power set of ${a, b}$",
        "answer": ["a"]
      },
      "q5": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "So, when you see $b$ in a sentence, it probably refers to:",
        "answer": "The character ‘$b$’.",
        "choices": ["The character ‘$b$’.", "Some string named ‘$b$’."]
      },
      "q5_1": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "And if y see w in a sentence, it probably refers to ",
        "answer": "Some string given the name ‘$w$’",
        "choices": ["The character ‘$w$’", "Some string given the name ‘$w$’"]
      },
      "q6": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "Let $w=abbc$, $v=ab$, What is $|w|$ + $|v|$",
        "answer": "6",
        "choices": ["6", "$k$"]
      },
      "q7": {
        "type": "textBox",
        "question": "Let $w = abc$, $v = 012$, What is $w∘v$?",
        "answer": "abc012"
      },
      "q7_1": {
        "type": "textBox",
        "question": "Let $w = abc$, $v = 012$, What is $wv$?",
        "answer": "abc012"
      },
      "q8": {
        "type": "select",
        "question": "let $v = ab$, what is $v3$ ?",
        "answer": ["$vvv$", "$v∘v∘v$", "$ababab$"],
        "choices": ["$vvv$", "$v∘v∘v$", "$ababab$"]
      },
      "q8_1": {
        "type": "textBox",
        "question": "Is this a language? {$\\lambda$}",
        "answer": "yes"
      },
      "q9": {
        "type": "textBox",
        "question": "What is $\\lambda∘acb∘\\lambda$?",
        "answer": "acb"
      },
      "q10": {
        "type": "textBox",
        "question": "Let $w = abbc$, what is $w^R$?",
        "answer": "cbba"
      },
      "q11": {
        "type": "textBox",
        "question": "let $w=abbc$, and $v=ab$. What is $|vv^Rw|$",
        "answer": "8"
      },
      "q12": {
        "type": "select",
        "question": "Which of the following are strings in $\\Sigma∗$?",
        "answer": ["$\\lambda$", "a", "b", "aa", "abbabb"],
        "choices": ["$\\lambda$", "a", "b", "aa", "abbabb", "aaabababcc"]
      },
      "q12_1": {
        "type": "select",
        "question": "Which are examples of $w*$ where $w = abc$?",
        "answer": ["$Λ$", "$abc$", "$abcabc$"],
        "choices": ["$Λ$", "$abc$", "$abcabc$", "$aabbcc$"]
      },
      "q13": {
        "type": "select",
        "question": "Let  $//lambda$ = {$a,b$}, Which of the following are strings in ?",
        "answer": ["$a$", "$b$", "$aa$", "$abbabb$"],
        "choices": [
          "$\\lambda$",
          "$a$",
          "$b$",
          "$aa$",
          "$abbabb$",
          "$aaabababcc$"
        ]
      },
      "q14": {
        "type": "textBox",
        "question": " Let $\\sigma$={$a$,$b$,$c$}, $L1$={$ab$,$bc$,$aba$}, $L2$={$c$,$bc$,$bcc$}, What is $L1∪L2$ ?",
        "answer": "ab,bc,aba,c,bcc"
      },
      "q15": {
        "type": "textBox",
        "question": "Let //sigma={$a$,$b$,$c$}, $L1$={$ab$,$bc$,$aba$}, $L2$={$c$,$bc$,$bcc$}, What is $L1∩L2$ ?",
        "answer": "{bc}"
      },
      "q16": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "What is ?",
        "answer": [" "],
        "choices": [" "]
      },
      "q17": {
        "type": "textBox",
        "question": "What states can be combined?",
        "answer": "{abc,abbc,abbcc,bcc,bcbc,bcbcc,abac,ababc,ababcc}"
      },
      "q18": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "question": "Let //sigma={$a$,$b$}, $L1$={$ab$,$aba$}, What is $L0$?",
        "answer": ["{$λ$}"],
        "choices": ["{$λ$}", "{}<Empty set>", "$λ$"]
      },
      "q19": {
        "type": "textBox",
        "question": "Let //sigma={$a$,$b4}, $L1$={$ab$,$aba$}, What is $L2$? ",
        "answer": "{abab, ababa, abaab, abaaba}"
      },
      "q19_1": {
        "type": "textBox",
        "question": "Let //sigma={$a$,$b$}, $L1$={$ab$,$aba$}, What is $L3$?",
        "answer": "{ababab, ababaab, abaabab, abaabaab, abababa, ababaaba, abaababa, abaabaaba}"
      }
    }
  }
}
